// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What does HTML stand for?",
    answer: "Hyper Text Markup Language",
    options: [
      "Hyper Text Preprocessor",
      "Hyper Text Markup Language",
      "Hyper Text Multiple Language",
      "Hyper Tool Multi Language"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which of the following is used to create Web Pages ?",
    answer: "HTML",
    options: [
      "C++",
      "Java",
      "HTML",
      "JVM"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: " HTML is a set of markup",
    answer: " tags",
    options: [
      "sets",
      "tags",
      "attributes",
      "none of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: " HTML tags are used to describe document ",
    answer: "content",
    options: [
      "definition",
      "content",
      " language",
      "model"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "HTML program is saved using ______ extension.",
    answer: "html",
    options: [
      ".htmn",
      "html",
      "htmnl",
      "htlm"
    ]
  },
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....
   {
    numb: 6,
  question: "HTML program can be read and rendered by _______.",
  answer: "Web Browser",
   options: [
     "Compiler",
    "Server",
      "Web Browser",
     "Interpreter"
   ]
},
{
  numb: 7,
question: " HTML tags are surrounded by _____ brackets.",
answer: "Angle",
 options: [
   "Curly",
  "Angle",
    " Round",
   "Squart"
 ]
},
{
  numb: 8,
question: " HTML document can contain _______.",
answer: "All the above",
 options: [
   "Tags",
  "Plain Text",
    "Attributes",
   "All the above"
 ]
},
{
  numb: 9,
question: "Page designed in HTML is called as _________.",
answer: " Web page",
 options: [
   "Server Page",
  " Web page",
    "Media Page",
   " none of the above"
 ]
},
{
  numb: 10,
question: " Which of the following is the first web browser ?",
answer: " Nexus",
 options: [
   "Netscape Navigator",
  "Internet Explorer",
    " Nexus",
   "Mosaic"
 ]
},
{
  numb: 11,
question: "Who created the first web browser ?",
answer: "Tim Berners Lee",
 options: [
   "Jacobs",
  "Tim Berners Lee",
    "Marc Andeersen",
   "Mozilla foundation"
 ]
},
{
  numb: 12,
question: "We can write HTML code using ________.",
answer: "All the above",
 options: [
   "Microsoft Word",
  "Notepad",
    "Notepad++",
   "All the above"
 ]

},
{
  numb: 13,
question: "PC running with Windows 3.x will have _______ extension for HTML page.",
answer: " .htm",
 options: [
   ".html",
  " .htm",
    ".tml",
   ".httm"
 ]
},
{
  numb: 14,
question: "Fundamental blocks in HTML is called as ________.",
answer: "HTML Tag",
 options: [
   "HTML Attribute",
  "HTML Body",
    "HTML Tag",
   "HTML Element"
 ]
},
{
  numb: 15,
question: "HTML is considered as __________.",
answer: "Markup Language",
 options: [
   "High Level Language",
  "OOP Language",
    "Programming Language",
   "Markup Language"
 ]
},
{
  numb: 16,
question: " _______ attribute is used to specify where to open the linked document.",
answer: "target",
 options: [
   "target",
  "coords",
    "rel",
   "none of the above"
 ]
},
{
  numb: 17,
question: " Which of the anchor attribute is used to specify the language of the linked document ?",
answer: "hreflang",
 options: [
   "alang",
  "lang",
    "hreflang",
   " all the above"
 ]
},
{
  numb: 18,
question: "The _____ attribute is used to specify MIME type of the linked document.",
answer: "Type",
 options: [
   "Type",
  "Media",
    "none of the above",
   "xml"
 ]
},
{
  numb: 19,
question: "HTML links can be styled using ______.",
answer: " CSS",
 options: [
   "XML",
  " CSS",
    "JavaScript",
   "PHP"
 ]
},
{
  numb: 20,
question: "Which is smallest Heading Tag in HTML ?",
answer: "H6",
 options: [
   "H1",
  "H2",
    "H5",
   "H6"
 ]
},
];